catsofaustralia.com 2013-05-20

# Cats of Australia Privacy Policy

> **Privacy Policy for catsofaustralia.com**
> 
> catsofaustralia.com **** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your  privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:  [ www.catsofaustralia.com](http://www.catsofaustralia.com/)
> 
> **Information Automatically Logged** Cookies: Our site uses cookies. You may notice things like forum systems show your username when you enter. This is done with cookies. We also use cookies to show if content has changed since your last visit to that site, or area of a site.
> 
> **Registration Forms**
> 
> catsofaustralia.com collects data on users via registration forms on our site in which we ask visitors for general contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code).  **
> 
> External Links
> 
> ** This site contains links to other sites.  catsofaustralia.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 
> 
> **Public Forums** This site makes  forums available to our members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Our forums require the collection of personal information (including but not limited to name, email address, location, and ip address). This information is used solely to insure any users violating our content rules can be contacted.
> 
> catsofaustralia.com respects the privacy of all visitors/users of the site. If for any reason you contact us via e-mail, or become a member of our forums, your contact details will remain confidential to the site owner & site staff only. The only exception to this would be if  catsofaustralia.com was legally ordered to disclose information on a member.
> 
> **Legal Disclosures of Information**
> 
> catsofaustralia.com will not share any personally identifiable information collected from visitors or members of the site unless the following reasons apply.
> 
> 1) We are legally ordered to provide such information via a legal subpoena.
> 
> 2) We have reason to believe that a member has endangered, threatened, harassed another member or staff member
> 
> We also use third party advertisements on  catsofaustralia.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
> 
> Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
>  Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). For information on DART cookies click [ here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)
> 
> You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
> 
> Please contact  [ catsofaustralia.com administration](mailto:zoe@catsofaustralia.com) **** with any queries
